Hikari-chan.
ひかりちゃん
yes.
はい
This time, I'm going to eat Hikari-chan's perverted kami.
今度はさ、 ひかりちゃんの 変態カミ食うじゃん
Can you bully me?
いじめていってもらえる?
I will do my best.
頑張ります
I don't know if I can do it though.
できるかどうかわからないけど
So cute, use your face and body to make yourself feel good.
そのかわいいさ、 顔と体使って気持ちよくしてよ
yes.
はい
I want you to lick my whole body.
体じゃいっぱい舐めてほしい
May I?
いいですか?
Because you're licking me so disgustingly
そんな嫌らしく舐められるんだから
Na.
な
Ah, lick there.
あ、 そこペロペロ
Pe
ペ
Ro pero.
ロ ペロ
My stomach hurts.
お腹が痛いね
Are you having trouble with something?
なんかタブルしてんの?
That's what happens.
そうなっちゃうんだ
Well, by the way, it's fun.
てか、ちなみに楽しいね
Twitch.
ピクピクして
Look at that naughty face.
そのエッチな顔もっていっぱい見して
What would you like to do if you were this big?
こんなでっかくなったら何したくなる?
Makes me want to see it.
見れたくなっちゃう
I want to see it.
見れたくなるんだ
i want to eat?
食べたい?
this.
これ
I'm sure you'll just lick it.
きっとだけペロペロして
Pe
ペ
Ro pero.
ロ ペロして
I want this person to do it, I say.
この人やってほしいわね、言う
Stick out your tongue and strain your tongue.
舌出していっぱい舌こしこして
Look here.
こっち見て
It's getting fuller.
パンパンになってきたな
Give me a lick, please
ペロペロしてあげて、いっぱ
stomach.
い
Hold your tongue up and strain your tongue.
舌 立てていっぱい舌こしこして
I'm squeezing out a lot of sperm.
精子いっぱい絞りてるんだよ
that's why.
だから
Squeeze a lot.
すごいいっぱい絞って
It will come out when you wash your hands.
洗面すると出ちゃうよ
Sperm.
精 子
Kuro-chan, this mouth feels so good.
黒ちゃん気持ちいいな、この口
Let me out, Kuro-chan.
出してね、黒ちゃん
Would you like to talk to this cute girl?
この可愛い口出す?
It has become very chubby.
すごいパンパンになってきた
It's not finished, Kuro-chan.
出来上がらず、黒ちゃん
I still have to lick it off.
まだ舐めてはずしちゃう
Kuro-chan, give me more.
黒ちゃん、もっと出せ
mouth.
口
Give me more.
もっといっぱい出せ
I really can't bring it out.
めっちゃに出せない
Don't give it all out.
全部出さない
Have you squeezed it all out?
全部絞り取った?
real?
ほんと?
Well then, say "bae".
じゃあ、ベーって口にして
I tried my best to speak.
頑張って喋ったんだ
The sperm came out.
精子出てきたね